dropshipdesign.com 2010-02-10

# DropshipDesign.com LLC - Start your own Wholesale & Dropship Business. Sell Our products anywhere, you keep all the profits!

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.dropshipdesign.com&sealid=101) LAST UPDATED ON FRIDAY, FEBRUARY 09, 2007 

The privacy of those who visit our Web site is of primary concern to DropshipDesign.com LLC. Your personal privacy and the security of your personal data are a primary concern to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide you with this policy page where we disclose and explain our online information practices. This page can be found by clicking on the Privacy Policy link available on the links located in the footer of our home page. 

Dropshipdesign.com LLC is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build userâ€™s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site dropshipdesign.com and dsdsecure.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our management team at sales@dropshipdesign.com. You may also send us a written letter at the following address: 

DropshipDesign.com LLC  
1100 Dexter Avenue North,   
Suite 100, Seattle, WA 98109 

If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

Use of Information 

When you register with our website, we ask for your full name, address, telephone number and credit card information so we can process your order. None of this information is shared with outside parties other than companies we employ to perform functions on our behalf, to which limited data is given in order to provide you with optional marketing assistance. We also use this information to process your orders, conduct account verifications, and to communicate with you about the status of your orders. We will use your contact information to contact you should we have a problem with processing an order. 

We also use your email address to send you special notifications regarding new products, new releases as well as occasional scheduled downtimes for maintenance purposes. 

DropshipDesign.com also reserves the right to disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number and email address as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud or other unlawful activity. Specifically, this includes exchanging such information with other companies and organizations for collection of unpaid funds, law enforcement agencies and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights. 

In order to provide you with marketing assistance, we will share your contact information with a trusted third party that will contact you after registration. This third party company will offer you marketing assistance based on your needs. Your personal information will not be shared with any other company except our service providers. You can opt to not be contacted by simply sending us an email at sales@dropshipdesign.com. 

You may not opt out of our service-related announcements and for our new products and feature announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You may also receive an email when we deploy a new version with new features. You may opt out of receiving a call from the mentoring service by contacting us at 1-800-921-0136 OR by creating a ticket with our online support system by clicking on the CONTACT US link. 

We use PayPal to facilitate our order/payment processing as well as Authorize.net to process payments through Visa and Master Card. If you choose the PayPal method of payment, then you will be automatically transferred to PayPal's site in the case of PayPal payments. Please be aware that their privacy policy governs the use and collection of the information and is shared back with us to fulfill the order. If you choose the credit card method of payment, then you will be redirected to our secure page under the domain name dsdsecure.com where we will capture your name, address and credit card information. Your credit card information will be transmitted to our merchant account provider to verify that your information is accurate, which is referred to as an AVS check. We will not store your credit card information and your order will be processed after the AVS check is positive. The page on which you will enter our credit card information will be hosted under the domain name dsdsecure.com and will be using a secure socket layer (SSL) which encrypts all your credit card information. This will ensure complete privacy of your credit card information and will not use your information for their own marketing purpose. 

Our affiliate program will allow you to resell our dropship plans in exchange for commissions. Once you signup for the free affiliate program, we will pay your commissions on a monthly basis via a deposit to your PayPal account. We will not share your personal information entered in the affiliate signup page with any third parties who are not agents or service providers. 

Testimonials 

On occasion we will post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name only. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. You can have your testimonial removed from our website by simply sending us an email at sales@dropshipdesign.com or by creating a ticket by clicking on the CONTACT US link. 

Cookies 

Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored on your hard drive. As you browse our website, cookies might be placed on your computer hard drive to maintain certain information about your current session. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Third party cookies will be used for the purpose of supporting the LIVE CHAT only and they will not be tied to any of your personal identifiable information. 

Security and Access 

Our website takes every possible precaution to protect our memberâ€™s personal information. During the transmission of your payment information, we use a secure server which uses secure socket layer technology (SSL), which encrypts all of your payment information. This will ensure complete privacy of your data. The secure pages involve the signup form, the profile page where you can update your personal information, the shopping cart and the final payment page on which you will enter your credit card information. We will not store your credit card information and we will not initiate any automatic charges to your credit card. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

In the case where you will be selling products on third party websites, such as eBay, we will require that you confirm your billing address before allowing you to place orders with a shipping address different from your billing address. You will be presented with an address verification FORM in the home page of the memberâ€™s area which needs to be printed and signed. Once we have confirmed your billing address, we will change the status of your membership to VERIFIED which will allow you to place orders using the shipping address of your buyers. Please note that this verification process will be required only once. We apply this security policy to protect both ourselves and our members from attempts to use funds from unauthorized sources. 

Correcting and updating your personal information 

All your personal information can be accessed and updated from the profile page. This page will be accessible to you only from the memberâ€™s login area. Any changes made to your personal information will trigger the system to change the status of your membership to â€œunverifiedâ€. You will be required to confirm your billing address once more in order to dropship merchandise to addresses different from your billing address. 

If you prefer to remove your information, simply cancel your membership and your account will be removed from our system. You can cancel your membership at anytime by sending us a cancellation request through our online ticketing system by clicking on the CONTACT US link located at the top of the website OR you can simply ignore the renewal notice once the 12 months are over and your account will automatically be closed. 

Third party links to other websites 

The DropshipDesign.com site may have links to other Web sites on the Internet that are not owned or controlled by DropshipDesign.com LLC. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of these Web sites, nor does this mean that DropshipDesign.com endorses them in any way. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
